http://www.innohep.com/privacy-policy

Print
Share
Email
Data Privacy Policy
This privacy statement describes our current policies and practices with regard to Personal Data collected by us from you directly and/or through the Website. For the purpose of the Data Privacy Policy, “we”, “us”, “our” means LEO Pharma A/S and LEO Laboratories Limited. When you register for the CancerClot Patient Support Service through this Website you give your explicit consent to us collecting and using the information as set out in APPENDIX 1 to this Privacy Policy.Before you submit any information through this Website you must read this Privacy Policy and the Consent Form below and give your explicit consent to the use of your personal data in accordance with the Privacy Policy and Consent Form.The term "Personal Data" refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, birthday, health information, e-mail address or mailing address and telephone number.Data Privacy – Use of collected personal information about youPersonal Data submitted on our Website will be kept confidential and will only be used for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy and in the consent form.We may use your Personal Data: To administer the Website and our business including statistical analysis  To enable your use of the services available on the Website  To personalise your visit to the Website, assist you while you use the Website and deal with your comments and respond to your queries  To contact you via email, SMS, telephone or by ordinary mail if you have requested this  To carry out surveys, studies and evaluations  To understand who uses the Website and how and to better understand needs and interests of visitors and users in order to improve the Website  To comply with applicable laws, regulations or codes of practice  For all other purposes to which you have consentedData Privacy – How is your personal information secured?To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.The employees who have access to Personal Data have been trained to handle such data properly and in accordance with our security protocols and strict standards of confidentiality. Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we take appropriate measures to try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. You understand and hereby consent that your Personal Data will be made accessible: To LEO Laboratories Limited, LEO Pharma A/S and any other LEO Pharma Group company  To third parties providing technical support (e.g., hosting services)  To third party service providers assisting LEO Pharma Group companies or to send communications to you  To any proposed assignee, transferee or purchaser of a LEO Pharma Group company that processes your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy  To any governmental, administrative, judicial or regulatory authority to co-operate in proceedings, inquiries and investigations by such authorities or to comply with any legal or regulatory requirementsYou understand that these recipients may be located in countries outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including in the United States of America, which may not have laws equivalent to data protection laws in the EEA.Data Privacy – Your rights and responsibilitiesYou may request us or any third party instructed by us to:  Provide you with information on the Personal Data that are being processed about you; the purposes of the processing; the categories of recipients of the data; and any available information as to the source of such data
Correct, erase or block Personal Data we or any third party instructed by us hold about you if these turn out to be inaccurate or misleading  If you have requested to receive information from us, e.g. newsletters etc., and do not wish to be receive further information, you can easily opt out of receiving further information from us by sending an email to the address set out at the end of this Privacy Policy.If the Personal Data we, or any third party instructed by us, have about you changes please let us know as soon as possible so that we can keep our records up to date.Data ControllersThe data controllers responsible for this Website are LEO Laboratories Limited and LEO Pharma A/S.QuestionsIf you have any queries concerning this Privacy Policy, how we use your Personal Data or should you wish to exercise any of your data protection rights please contact the Head of Quality, Compliance & Data Protection at:APPENDIX 1: CONSENT FORMWe understand that your privacy is important to you, and we are committed to maintaining the privacy, security and accuracy of your Personal Data.Data Collection and Processing for the Purposes of participation in the CancerClot Patient Support ServiceIf you register for the CancerClot Patient Support Service you understand and hereby explicitly consent that LEO Laboratories Limited, LEO Pharma A/S and any affiliate within the LEO Pharma Group may collect, process or use Personal Data about you as set out in this consent form and the Privacy Policy. This will include, but not be limited to, the following Personal Data (the “Patient Support Data”): Your contact information, including name, address, phone number and email address  Your gender, age and disease
Duration of your treatmentThe CancerClot Database will be hosted centrally by LEO Pharma A/S using a service provider in Denmark. In the future we may decide to host the data at a LEO Pharma Group company or another service provider. The Patient Support Data will be processed for the following purposes: To provide patient support services according to individual profiles based on individually keyed in data processed by an algorithm and to contact you  To provide anonymised feedback to HCPs, associations and other parties in the health care system
To improve the CancerClot Patient Support Service in terms of functionality, content and innovation
To report adverse events to LEO Pharma Group companies and health regulators using de-identified dataWe may send you communications regarding patient support services by e-mail, SMS or by other electronic means. You consent to such communications and understand that we may use a service provider to assist in sending you such communications and that standard text and data charges may apply.Comments and QuestionsYou may use any form or commenting system provided within the CancerClot website. All comments or questions will be moderated by LEO Pharma. By commenting or submitting a form, you grant LEO Pharma permission to contact you regarding the content of the comment. If you consent in writing (including by email), you also grant LEO Pharma license to modify, edit, crop, highlight and/or republish your content with attribution to you, or if requested by you, publish without attribution to you in an anonymous form.Transfer of Patient Support DataYou understand and hereby explicitly consent that your Patient Support Data may be made accessible:  To LEO Laboratories Limited, LEO Pharma A/S and any other LEO Pharma Group company  To third parties providing technical support (e.g., hosting services) in relation to the CancerClot Database  To third party service providers assisting LEO Pharma Group Companies with the maintenance and development of the CancerClot concept and platform or to send communications to you  To any proposed assignee, transferee or purchaser of a LEO Pharma Group company that processes Patient Support Data in accordance with this consent form  To any governmental, administrative, judicial or regulatory authority to co-operate in proceedings, inquiries and investigations by such authorities or to comply with any legal or regulatory requirements
You understand that these recipients may be located in countries outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including in the United States of America, which may not have laws equivalent to data protection laws in the EEA.An overview of all LEO Pharma Group Companies as well as company addresses is available on www.leo-pharma.com and you should check this site regularly.Information, Correction, Deletion or Blocking of Personal Data / Withdrawal of ConsentThe Patient Support Data is provided by you on a voluntary basis; not providing Patient Support Data may mean that we may not be able to provide you with an individualised Patient Support Service.You have the right, at any time, to request access to the information which we have about you. You also have the right to request at any time the correction, deletion or blocking of your Patient Support Data in accordance with applicable data protection laws. Finally, you can, at any time, withdraw your consent with future effect without the need to state any reason. We will not charge costs or fees for providing access to, or any correction, deletion or blocking of Patient Support Data.If you have any queries concerning this Data Privacy Policy, how we use your Patient Support Data or should you wish to exercise any of your data protection rights please contact the Data Protection Officer at LEO Pharma:LEO Pharma A/S, Industriparken 55, DK- 2750 Ballerup, Denmark, Telephone number: +45 4494 5888, E mail: leo.corporate@leo-pharma.com
Scroll to top
